<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Gyeeta Observability Blog</title>
        <link>https://gyeeta.io/blog</link>
        <description>A Blog describing features, use cases of Gyeeta Observability and monitoring in general</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <copyright>Exact Solutions, Inc.</copyright>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introducing Gyeeta]]></title>
            <link>https://gyeeta.io/blog/introducing-gyeeta</link>
            <guid>introducing-gyeeta</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We are very happy to introduce Gyeeta]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We are very happy to introduce <a href="https://github.com/gyeeta" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Gyeeta</a>
to help with meeting your organization's Observability and Monitoring needs.</p><p>We felt there was a need for a product like Gyeeta for the following reasons :</p><ul><li><p>Few tools exist currently in the Free and Open source Observability space which can be quickly deployed
without application changes and without any manual configuration.</p></li><li><p>Commercial SaaS tools exist which utilize a combination of APM, Tracing, Kernel Monitors, eBPF
to provide a rich variety of metrics but these products are expensive both in terms of costs as
well as Host CPU, Memory and IO usage and require manual configuration in many cases as well.</p></li></ul><p>We felt there was the need for a product which was Free, Open source and which organizations could
use to monitor their Infrastructure 24x7 non-intrusively, with minimal overhead and without any
application changes and which would not need any manual configuration.</p><p>This requires a tool which would be very lightweight in terms of resource usage and importantly,
provide quick Alerts or Search results to detect any anomaly or degradation.</p><p>We hope you try Gyeeta in your environment and find it a useful product.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>introduction</category>
            <category>welcome</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>